[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "Is 2345888 a perfect square?",
    "options": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "Square of 16 equals",
    "options": ["256", "296", "286", "266"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "Which of the following numbers are perfect squares?",
    "options": ["133", "1570", "1092", "1024"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "Without actual addition find the sum of first 20 odd numbers",
    "options": ["425", "600", "400", "360"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "What is 4 squared?",
    "options": ["2", "4", "8", "16"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "What is the value of 3 × 2<sup>2</sup>?",
    "options": ["6", "9", "12", "8"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "What is the value of 6<sup>2</sup> × 2<sup>2</sup>?",
    "options": ["36", "144", "248", "324"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "Which of the following is a square of an even number?",
    "options": ["121", "169", "196", "225"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "Which of the following is a square of an odd number?",
    "options": ["225", "196", "144", "100"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "What is 85²?",
    "options": ["7025", "7225", "7425", "7525"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q11",
    "question": "What is the square of 105?",
    "options": ["11025", "10125", "11525", "12025"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q12",
    "question": "What is the square of 986?",
    "options": ["976196", "972196", "962196", "974196"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q13",
    "question": "What is the square of 306 using Vedic Maths?",
    "options": ["95636", "93616", "94636", "93636"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q14",
    "question": "Which of the following pairs are perfect squares that sum up to 29?",
    "options": ["1 and 24", "4 and 25", "4 and 16", "9 and 16"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q15",
    "question": "Without adding, find the sum of the first 6 odd numbers.",
    "options": ["28", "30", "36", "44"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q16",
    "question": "Without adding, what is the following sum:<br> 1 + 3 + 5 + 7 + 9 + 11 + 13 + 15",
    "options": ["49", "56", "60", "64"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q17",
    "question": "Total numbers between 100² and 101² = _____",
    "options": ["200", "204", "208", "400"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q18",
    "question": "The greatest 3-digit number which is a perfect square is",
    "options": ["961", "962", "963", "978"],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
